RUPINDER PAL SINGH

Full Stack Developer with 3+ years of experience in building scalable web applications using modern development stack. I have experience in teaching programming to college students. Worked for various clients over the years on freelance projects to help them to achieve their business goals.

6-3235 rue de Rouen, Montreal, QC, Canada H1W-1K9 (438) 998-1746 rupindervirdi96@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Montreal, Quebec, CA

July2019 - Present

I make projects for college students. Projects range from online resumes to full stack web applications.

Enrage Tech, Jalandhar, India — Front End Developer

Sept2015 - May2018

Worked closely with professional designers to provide strong UI Experience. Helped various clients

EDUCATION

College LaSalle, Montreal, Quebec, CA — <u>IT Programmer</u> <u>Analyst</u>

Jan2019 - Jun2021

#ADVANCED-OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING #JAVASCRIPT

#WEB-DEVELOPMENT #ASP.NET #JAVA #IOS #ANDROID #MULTI-TIER

APPLICATIONS #DATABASE

Guru Nanak Dev University, Jalandhar, India — <u>Bachelors in</u> <u>Computer Science</u>

June2014 - June2017

#OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING #WEB-DESIGNING #JAVA

#WEB-DEVELOPMENT #OPERATING-SYSTEMS #C++ #ALGORITHMS

#MATHEMATICS #JQUERY

SOCIAL PRESENCE

GITHUB | CODEPEN | PORTFOLIO | INSTAGRAM

SKILLS

FrontEnd: HTML, JavaScript,

CSS, SCSS.

BackEnd: NODE.js, JAVA, PYTHON, PHP, SQL.

Frameworks: REACT.js,

VUE.js.

Database: MongoDB, MySQL,Firebase.

Design: Figma, Adobe PhotoShop, Adobe XD.

Languages: C++, C#.

PROJECTS

- Facebook-Clone
- Whatsapp-Clone
- Hangman
- Reactor
- Issues-Tracker